{
    "id": "6c4b26e070ae488f82f3a0686a5e0f13",
    "title": "Grammar And Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The travellers rested under a …………………….. of trees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "choir",
                "clump",
                "clan"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "While taking a stroll in my garden, I was attacked by a ………………………… of bees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "swarm",
                "group",
                "cluster"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What will you do if you find an abandoned ………………………….. of kittens?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "troupe",
                "litter",
                "band"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of these novels ……………………… worth reading.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The children were accompanied …………………….. their mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I found ……………………….. empty bottle floating on the water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "an",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He, as well as I, ……………………….. great interest in politics.",
            "description": "When we connect two nouns with as well as, the verb agrees with the former. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The minister unlike his sons ……………………… honest.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun minister.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Close the door. Change into passive",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Door be closed.",
                "Be the door closed.",
                "Let the door be closed."
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Either you or your brother ……………………….. to clean the room.",
            "description": "When two singular nouns are connected with either/or, the verb agrees with the latter.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither my brother nor my sisters ……………………. married.",
            "description": "When two singular nouns are connected with either/or, the verb agrees with the latter.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the female of fox …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Foxen",
                "Foxess",
                "Vixen"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}